<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="FOOT">
	     A unit of length equal to 0.3048 metres 
	     (standard name ft).
	</string>
	
	<string name="YARD">
	     A unit of length equal to 0.9144 metres
	     (standard name yd).
	</string>
	
	<string name="INCH">
	     A unit of length equal to 0.0254 metres
	     (standard name in).
	</string>
	
	<string name="MILE">
	     A unit of length equal to 1609.344 metres
	     (standard name mi).
	</string>
	
	<string name="NAUTICAL_MILE">
	     A unit of length equal to 1852.0 metres
	     (standard name nmi).
	</string>
	
	<string name="ANGSTROM">
	     A unit of length equal to 1E-10 metres
	     (standard name Å).
	</string>
	
	<string name="ASTRONOMICAL_UNIT">
	     A unit of length equal to the average distance from the center of the
	     Earth to the center of the Sun (standard name ua).
	</string>
	
	<string name="LIGHT_YEAR">
	     A unit of length equal to the distance that light travels in one year
	     through a vacuum (standard name ly).
	</string>
	
	<string name="PARSEC">
	     A unit of length equal to the distance at which a star would appear to
	     shift its position by one arcsecond over the course the time
	     (about 3 months) in which the Earth moves a distance of
	     one Astronomical Unit in the direction perpendicular to the
	     direction to the star (standard name pc).
	</string>
	
	<string name="POINT">
	     A unit of length equal to 0.013837 inches exactly
	     (standard name pt).
	</string>
	
	<string name="PIXEL">
	     A unit of length equal to 1/72 INCH
	     (standard name pixel).
	     It is the American point rounded to an even 1/72 inch.
	</string>
	
	<string name="COMPUTER_POINT">
	     Equivalent to one Pixel
	</string>
	
	<string name="MINUTE">
	     A unit of duration equal to 60 seconds
	     (standard name min).
	</string>
	
	<string name="HOUR">
	     A unit of duration equal to 60 minutes
	     (standard name h).
	</string>
	
	<string name="DAY">
	     A unit of duration equal to 24 hours
	     (standard name d).
	</string>
	
	<string name="WEEK">
	     A unit of duration equal to 7 days
	     (standard name week).
	</string>
	
	<string name="YEAR">
	     A unit of duration equal to 365 days, 5 hours, 49 minutes,
	     and 12 seconds (standard name year).
	</string>
	
	<string name="MONTH">
	     A unit of duration equal to one twelfth of a year
	     (standard name month).
	</string>
	
	<string name="DAY_SIDEREAL">
	     A unit of duration equal to the time required for a complete rotation of
	     the earth in reference to any star or to the vernal equinox at the
	     meridian, equal to 23 hours, 56 minutes, 4.09 seconds
	     (standard name day_sidereal).
	</string>
	
	<string name="YEAR_SIDEREAL">
	     A unit of duration equal to one complete revolution of the
	     earth about the sun, relative to the fixed stars, or 365 days, 6 hours,
	     9 minutes, 9.54 seconds (standard name year_sidereal).
	</string>
	
	<string name="YEAR_CALENDAR">
	     A unit of duration equal to 365 days
	     (standard name year_calendar).
	</string>
	
	<string name="ATOMIC_MASS">
	     A unit of mass equal to 1/12 the mass of the carbon-12 atom
	     (standard name u).
	</string>
	
	<string name="ELECTRON_MASS">
	     A unit of mass equal to the mass of the electron
	     (standard name me).
	</string>
	
	<string name="POUND">
	     A unit of mass equal to 453.59237 grams (avoirdupois pound,
	     standard name lb).
	</string>
	
	<string name="OUNCE">
	     A unit of mass equal to 1/16 pound
	     (standard name oz).
	</string>
	
	<string name="TON_US">
	     A unit of mass equal to 2000 pounds (short ton, 
	     standard name ton_us).
	</string>
	
	<string name="TON_UK">
	     A unit of mass equal to 2240 pounds (long ton,
	     standard name ton_uk).
	</string>
	
	<string name="METRIC_TON">
	     A unit of mass equal to 1000 kilograms (metric ton,
	     standard name t).
	</string>
	
	<string name="E">
	     A unit of electric charge equal to the charge on one electron
	     (standard name e).
	</string>
	
	<string name="FARADAY">
	     A unit of electric charge equal to equal to the product of Avogadro\'s
	     number and the charge (1e) on a single electron
	     (standard name Fd).
	</string>
	
	<string name="FRANKLIN">
	     A unit of electric charge which exerts a force of one dyne on an equal
	     charge at a distance of one centimeter
	     (standard name Fr).
	</string>
	
	<string name="RANKINE">
	     A unit of temperature equal to 5/9 °K
	     (standard name °R).
	</string>
	
	<string name="FAHRENHEIT">
	     A unit of temperature equal to degree Rankine minus 
	     459.67 °R (standard name °F).
	</string>
	
	<string name="REVOLUTION">
	     A unit of angle equal to a full circle or 2PI 
	     radian (standard name rev).
	</string>
	
	<string name="DEGREE_ANGLE">
	     A unit of angle equal to 1/360 revolution
	     (standard name °).
	</string>
	
	<string name="MINUTE_ANGLE">
	     A unit of angle equal to 1/60 degree angle
	     (standard name ′).
	</string>
	
	<string name="SECOND_ANGLE">
	      A unit of angle equal to 1/60 minute angle
	     (standard name ").
	</string>
	
	<string name="CENTIRADIAN">
	     A unit of angle equal to 0.01 radian
	     (standard name centiradian).
	</string>
	
	<string name="GRADE">
	     A unit of angle measure equal to 1/400 revolution
	     (standard name grade).
	</string>
	
	<string name="MILES_PER_HOUR 
	        ">
	     A unit of velocity expressing the number of international miles per hour (abbreviation mph).
	</string>
	
	<string name="KILOMETRES_PER_HOUR 
	        ">
	     A unit of velocity expressing the number of kilometres per 
	     HOUR hour.
	</string>
	
	<string name="KNOT 
	        ">
	     A unit of velocity expressing the number of
	     nautical miles per hour (abbreviation kn).
	</string>
	
	<string name="MACH">
	     A unit of velocity to express the speed of an aircraft relative to
	     the speed of sound (standard name Mach).
	</string>
	
	<string name="C">
	     A unit of velocity relative to the speed of light
	     (standard name c).
	</string>
	
	<string name="G">
	     A unit of acceleration equal to the gravity at the earth\'s surface
	     (standard name grav).
	</string>
	
	<string name="ARE">
	     A unit of area equal to 100 m²
	     (standard name a).
	</string>
	
	<string name="HECTARE">
	     A unit of area equal to 100 are
	     (standard name ha).
	</string>
	
	<string name="BYTE">
	     A unit of data amount equal to 8 bit
	     (Binary Term, standard name byte).
	</string>
	
	<string name="OCTET">
	     Equivalent BYTE
	</string>
	
	<string name="GILBERT">
	     A unit of electric charge equal to the centimeter-gram-second
	     electromagnetic unit of magnetomotive force, equal to 10/4
	     PIampere-turn (standard name Gi).
	</string>
	
	<string name="ERG">
	     A unit of energy equal to 1E-7 J
	     (standard name erg).
	</string>
	
	<string name="ELECTRON_VOLT">
	     A unit of energy equal to one electron-volt (standard name 
	     eV, also recognized keV, MeV, GeV).
	</string>
	
	<string name="LAMBERT">
	     A unit of illuminance equal to 1E4 Lx
	     (standard name La).
	</string>
	
	<string name="MAXWELL">
	     A unit of magnetic flux equal 1E-8 Wb
	     (standard name Mx).
	</string>
	
	<string name="GAUSS">
	     A unit of magnetic flux density equal 1000 A/m
	     (standard name G).
	</string>
	
	<string name="DYNE">
	     A unit of force equal to 1E-5 N
	     (standard name dyn).
	</string>
	
	<string name="KILOGRAM_FORCE">
	     A unit of force equal to 9.80665 N
	     (standard name kgf).
	</string>
	
	<string name="POUND_FORCE">
	     A unit of force equal to Pound·G
	     (standard name lbf).
	</string>
	
	<string name="HORSEPOWER">
	     A unit of power equal to the power required to raise a mass of 75
	     kilograms at a velocity of 1 meter per second (metric,
	     standard name hp).
	</string>
	
	<string name="ATMOSPHERE">
	     A unit of pressure equal to the average pressure of the Earth\'s
	     atmosphere at sea level (standard name atm).
	</string>
	
	<string name="BAR">
	     A unit of pressure equal to 100 kPa
	     (standard name bar).
	</string>
	
	<string name="MILLIMETER_OF_MERCURY">
	     A unit of pressure equal to the pressure exerted at the Earth\'s
	     surface by a column of mercury 1 millimeter high
	     (standard name mmHg).
	</string>
	
	<string name="INCH_OF_MERCURY">
	     A unit of pressure equal to the pressure exerted at the Earth\'s
	     surface by a column of mercury 1 inch high
	     (standard name inHg).
	</string>
	
	<string name="RAD">
	     A unit of radiation dose absorbed equal to a dose of 0.01 joule of
	     energy per kilogram of mass (J/kg) (standard name rd).
	</string>
	
	<string name="REM">
	     A unit of radiation dose effective equal to 0.01 Sv
	     (standard name rem).
	</string>
	
	<string name="CURIE">
	     A unit of radioctive activity equal to the activity of a gram of radium
	     (standard name Ci).
	</string>
	
	<string name="RUTHERFORD">
	     A unit of radioctive activity equal to 1 million radioactive
	     disintegrations per second (standard name Rd).
	</string>
	
	<string name="SPHERE">
	     A unit of solid angle equal to 4 PI steradians
	     (standard name sphere).
	</string>
	
	<string name="LITRE">
	     A unit of volume equal to one cubic decimeter (default label
	     L, also recognized µL, mL, cL, dL).
	</string>
	
	<string name="LITER">
	     Equivalent to LITRE (American spelling).
	</string>
	
	<string name="CUBIC_INCH">
	     A unit of volume equal to one cubic inch (in³).
	</string>
	
	<string name="GALLON_LIQUID_US">
	     A unit of volume equal to one US gallon, Liquid Unit. The U.S. liquid
	     gallon is based on the Queen Anne or Wine gallon occupying 231 cubic
	     inches (standard name gal).
	</string>
	
	<string name="QUART_LIQUID_US">
	     A unit of volume equal to one US quart, Liquid Unit.
	</string>
	
	<string name="PINT_LIQUID_US">
	     A unit of volume equal to one US pint, Liquid Unit.
	</string>
	
	<string name="OUNCE_LIQUID_US">
	     A unit of volume equal to 1 / 128 fluid gallon
	     (standard name oz_fl).
	</string>
	
	<string name="GALLON_DRY_US">
	     A unit of volume equal to one US dry gallon.
	     (standard name gallon_dry_us).
	</string>
	
	<string name="QUART_DRY_US">
	     A unit of volume equal to one US dry quart.
	</string>
	
	<string name="PINT_DRY_US">
	     A unit of volume equal to one US dry pint.
	</string>
	
	<string name="GALLON_UK">
	     A unit of volume equal to 4.546 09 LITRE
	     (standard name gal_uk).
	</string>
	
	<string name="OUNCE_LIQUID_UK">
	     A unit of volume equal to 1 / 160 gallon (uk)
	     (standard name oz_fl_uk).
	</string>
	
	<string name="POISE">
	     A unit of dynamic viscosity equal to 1 g/(cm·s)
	     (cgs unit).
	</string>
	
	<string name="STOKE">
	     A unit of kinematic viscosity equal to 1 cm²/s
	     (cgs unit).
	</string>
	
	<string name="ROENTGEN">
	     A unit used to measure the ionizing ability of radiation
	     (standard name Roentgen).
	</string>
	     
	<string name="AMPERE">
	     Default constructor (prevents this class from being instantiated).
	</string>
	
	<string name="CANDELA">
	     The base unit for luminous intensity quantities (cd).
	     The candela is the luminous intensity, in a given direction,
	     of a source that emits monochromatic radiation of frequency
	     540 × 1012 hertz and that has a radiant intensity in that
	     direction of 1/683 watt per steradian
	</string>
	
	<string name="KELVIN">
	     The base unit for thermodynamic temperature quantities (K).
	     The kelvin is the 1/273.16th of the thermodynamic temperature of the
	     triple point of water. It is named after the Scottish mathematician and
	     physicist William Thomson 1st Lord Kelvin (1824-1907)
	</string>
	
	<string name="KILOGRAM">
	     The base unit for mass quantities (kg).
	     It is the only SI unit with a prefix as part of its name and symbol.
	     The kilogram is equal to the mass of an international prototype in the
	     form of a platinum-iridium cylinder kept at Sevres in France.
	</string>
	
	<string name="METRE">
	     The base unit for length quantities (m).
	     One meter was redefined in 1983 as the distance traveled by light in
	     a vacuum in 1/299,792,458 of a second.
	</string>
	
	<string name="METER">
	     Equivalent to METRE (American spelling).
	</string>
	
	<string name="MOLE">
	     The base unit for amount of substance quantities (mol).
	     The mole is the amount of substance of a system which contains as many
	     elementary entities as there are atoms in 0.012 kilogram of carbon 12.
	</string>
	
	<string name="SECOND">
	     The base unit for duration quantities (s).
	     It is defined as the duration of 9,192,631,770 cycles of radiation
	     corresponding to the transition between two hyperfine levels of
	     the ground state of cesium (1967 Standard).
	</string>
	
	<string name="GRAM">
	     The derived unit for mass quantities (g).
	     The base unit for mass quantity is kilograms.
	</string>
	
	<string name="RADIAN">
	     The unit for plane angle quantities (rad).
	     One radian is the angle between two radii of a circle such that the
	     length of the arc between them is equal to the radius.
	</string>
	
	<string name="STERADIAN">
	     The unit for solid angle quantities (sr).
	     One steradian is the solid angle subtended at the center of a sphere by
	     an area on the surface of the sphere that is equal to the radius squared.
	     The total solid angle of a sphere is 4*Pi steradians.
	</string>
	
	<string name="BIT">
	     The unit for binary information (bit).
	</string>
	
	<string name="HERTZ">
	     The derived unit for frequency (Hz).
	     A unit of frequency equal to one cycle per second.
	     After Heinrich Rudolf Hertz (1857-1894), German physicist who was the
	     first to produce radio waves artificially.
	</string>
	
	<string name="NEWTON">
	     The derived unit for force (N).
	     One newton is the force required to give a mass of 1 kilogram an Force
	     of 1 metre per second per second. It is named after the English
	     mathematician and physicist Sir Isaac Newton (1642-1727).
	</string>
	
	<string name="PASCAL">
	     The derived unit for pressure, stress (Pa).
	     One pascal is equal to one newton per square meter. It is named after
	     the French philosopher and mathematician Blaise Pascal (1623-1662).
	</string>
	
	<string name="JOULE">
	     The derived unit for energy, work, quantity of heat (J).
	     One joule is the amount of work done when an applied force of 1 newton
	     moves through a distance of 1 metre in the direction of the force.
	     It is named after the English physicist James Prescott Joule (1818-1889).
	</string>
	
	<string name="WATT">
	     The derived unit for power, radiant, flux (W).
	     One watt is equal to one joule per second. It is named after the British
	     scientist James Watt (1736-1819).
	</string>
	
	<string name="COULOMB">
	     The derived unit for electric charge, quantity of electricity
	     (C).
	     One Coulomb is equal to the quantity of charge transferred in one second
	     by a steady current of one ampere. It is named after the French physicist
	     Charles Augustin de Coulomb (1736-1806).
	</string>
	
	<string name="VOLT">
	     The derived unit for electric potential difference, electromotive force
	     (V).
	     One Volt is equal to the difference of electric potential between two
	     points on a conducting wire carrying a constant current of one ampere
	     when the power dissipated between the points is one watt. It is named
	     after the Italian physicist Count Alessandro Volta (1745-1827).
	</string>
	
	<string name="FARAD">
	     The derived unit for capacitance (F).
	     One Farad is equal to the capacitance of a capacitor having an equal
	     and opposite charge of 1 coulomb on each plate and a potential difference
	     of 1 volt between the plates. It is named after the British physicist
	     and chemist Michael Faraday (1791-1867).
	</string>
	
	<string name="OHM">
	     The derived unit for electric resistance (Ω or 
	     Ohm).
	     One Ohm is equal to the resistance of a conductor in which a current of
	     one ampere is produced by a potential of one volt across its terminals.
	     It is named after the German physicist Georg Simon Ohm (1789-1854).
	</string>
	
	<string name="SIEMENS">
	     The derived unit for electric conductance (S).
	     One Siemens is equal to one ampere per volt. It is named after
	     the German engineer Ernst Werner von Siemens (1816-1892).
	</string>
	
	<string name="WEBER">
	     The derived unit for magnetic flux (Wb).
	     One Weber is equal to the magnetic flux that in linking a circuit of one
	     turn produces in it an electromotive force of one volt as it is uniformly
	     reduced to zero within one second. It is named after the German physicist
	     Wilhelm Eduard Weber (1804-1891).
	</string>
	
	<string name="TESLA">
	     The derived unit for magnetic flux density (T).
	     One Tesla is equal equal to one weber per square meter. It is named
	     after the Serbian-born American electrical engineer and physicist
	     Nikola Tesla (1856-1943).
	</string>
	
	<string name="HENRY">
	     The derived unit for inductance (H).
	     One Henry is equal to the inductance for which an induced electromotive
	     force of one volt is produced when the current is varied at the rate of
	     one ampere per second. It is named after the American physicist
	     Joseph Henry (1791-1878).
	</string>
	
	<string name="CELSIUS">
	     The derived unit for Celsius temperature (℃).
	     This is a unit of temperature such as the freezing point of water
	     (at one atmosphere of pressure) is 0 ℃, while the boiling point is
	     100 ℃.
	</string>
	
	<string name="LUMEN">
	     The derived unit for luminous flux (lm).
	     One Lumen is equal to the amount of light given out through a solid angle
	     by a source of one candela intensity radiating equally in all directions.
	</string>
	
	<string name="LUX">
	     The derived unit for illuminance (lx).
	     One Lux is equal to one lumen per square meter.
	</string>
	
	<string name="BECQUEREL">
	     The derived unit for activity of a radionuclide (Bq).
	     One becquerel is the radiation caused by one disintegration per second.
	     It is named after the French physicist, Antoine-Henri Becquerel
	     (1852-1908).
	</string>
	
	<string name="GRAY">
	     The derived unit for absorbed dose, specific energy (imparted), kerma
	     (Gy).
	     One gray is equal to the dose of one joule of energy absorbed per one
	     kilogram of matter. It is named after the British physician
	     L. H. Gray (1905-1965).
	</string>
	
	<string name="SIEVERT">
	     The derived unit for dose equivalent (Sv).
	     One Sievert is equal  is equal to the actual dose, in grays, multiplied
	     by a "quality factor" which is larger for more dangerous forms of
	     radiation. It is named after the Swedish physicist Rolf Sievert
	     (1898-1966).
	</string>
	
	<string name="KATAL">
	     The derived unit for catalytic activity (kat).
	</string>
	
	<string name="METRES_PER_SECOND">
	     The metric unit for velocity quantities (m/s).
	</string>
	
	<string name="METRES_PER_SQUARE_SECOND">
	     The metric unit for acceleration quantities (m/s²).
	</string>
	
	<string name="SQUARE_METRE">
	     The metric unit for area quantities (m²).
	</string>
	
	<string name="CUBIC_METRE">
	     The metric unit for volume quantities (m³).
	</string>
	
	<string name="KILOMETRE">
	     Equivalent to KILO(METRE).
	</string>
	
	<string name="CENTIMETRE">
	     Equivalent to CENTI(METRE).
	</string>
	
	<string name="MILLIMETRE">
	     Equivalent to MILLI(METRE).
	</string>
</resources>